<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Wanted For Thought Crime</title><link>https://wftc.xyz/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Wanted For Thought Crime</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:06:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://wftc.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Solving a cryptographic challenge in Rust</title><link>https://wftc.xyz/2020/01/crypto-rust/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 00:06:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wftc.xyz/2020/01/crypto-rust/</guid><description>Howdy Thought I&amp;rsquo;d kick things off by setting the tone for the rest of this blog. The front page description won&amp;rsquo;t do it justice as time passes and this nerdy diary of artless prose fills to the brim.
Getting closer to the point This isn&amp;rsquo;t to say that the blog is purely tech-based or security-related. Indeed it will be a recurring theme, largely due to how much less effort it takes to type stuff (code) and then type some more (this blog) to discuss said stuff.</description></item><item><title>Do not click!!1</title><link>https://wftc.xyz/2020/01/init.d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 17:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://wftc.xyz/2020/01/init.d/</guid><description>Title? Meh I used to believe my time management was spot on. Everything seemed within an arm&amp;rsquo;s reach, impeded only by my willpower and occasionally a desultory attitude. Poor young me, falling for traps like that is for the naive and credulous! I think know I can do better than this.
Naturally I&amp;rsquo;d want to change something about my habits and end this unabating love for procrastination. When moments of impending laziness arise, there is usually very little resistance on my behalf.</description></item></channel></rss>